hello everyone
and if you have been following my latest run
you know I haven't been passive anything
but I have been doing everything on demand
that caused a little bit of discussions
so I'm going to make this video to better explain why of this decision
and while the main reason was actually that I simply wanted to play in a different way than the usual Factorio Satisfactory way of making passive lines
I figured out this way is actually a little bit better
and right here I think we can see the main difference
I am currently in UHV
and my world base has a single Mega Distillation Tower
and especially in single player that means that
I won't have to upgrade a distillation tower for the platline
I won't have to upgrade a distillation tower for the naquadah-line
I won't have to upgrade a distillation tower for the netherite-line
I have a single Mega Distillation Tower to worry about
I think that could already sum up the whole video
but let's better see what it means to have a single machine for each kind of task
and also how to manage it
and at this point I realize that maybe I shouldn't even be finishing this video
one of the main reason for saying that is that I'm lazy and also I'm not good at explaining things
the main reason is that there isn't really anything to explain
it's just that for me now
it's more fun to build a single machine and figure out how to make patterns that work
rather than spamming machines where stuff goes in and stuff comes out
and while I was playing in this weird way
I realized it took me only half an hour to set up kevlar
which is way faster than when it took me one whole weekend to make a passive line dedicated to kevlar
and since I drastically reduced the amount of machines I have
it takes less time to upgrade those
and they also produce less lag
some people may argue that if I play that way
I will have more level containers
and those will be a source of lag
but I think that's only if you set those improperly
and I think that's it about this video
which was only about this different way of playing
a better explanation on how to do it I think belongs more to a AE2 or a GregTech tutorial video rather than this one
so see you next time
bye bye
大家好
如果你一直在关注我最近的一次跑步
你知道我什么都没做
但我一直在按要求做一切
这引起了一些讨论
所以我要制作这个视频来更好地解释这个决定的原因
虽然主要原因实际上是我只是想以一种不同于通常的因素令人满意的方式来制作被动线路
我发现这种方式实际上更好一点。
就在这里，我想我们可以看到主要的区别。
我目前在特高压
我的世界基地有一个大型蒸馏塔
尤其是在单人游戏中，这意味着
我就不用为平台升级蒸馏塔了
我就不用为naquadah生产线升级蒸馏塔了
我就不用为地狱石生产线升级蒸馏塔了
我要担心一座大型蒸馏塔
我想这已经可以总结整个视频了
但是让我们更好地看看每种任务都有一台机器意味着什么
以及如何管理它
在这一点上，我意识到也许我甚至不应该完成这个视频
这么说的主要原因之一是我很懒，也不擅长解释事情。
主要原因是没什么好解释的
只是现在对我来说
建造一台机器并弄清楚如何制作有效的模式更有趣
而不是垃圾邮件机，东西进东西出
当我以这种奇怪的方式演奏时
我意识到我只花了半个小时就布置好防弹衣
这比我花了一整个周末做一条凯夫拉尔专用无源线要快得多
由于我大幅减少了机器的数量
升级那些需要更少的时间
它们也产生更少的滞后
有些人可能会说如果我这么玩
我会有更多的水平容器
这些将是滞后的来源
但我认为只有在你设置不当的情况下
我想这就是这个视频。
这只是关于这种不同的游戏方式
关于如何做到这一点的更好解释，我认为更多的是属于AE2或gregtech教程视频，而不是这个。
所以下次见
拜拜